LAYLA ALMARWANI

7783864374

Laylaalmarwani.top@gmail.com



SKIILS

React HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap and jQuery Ruby on Rails, Node.js And Express

DATABASE

PostgreSQL

DEVELOPMENT & OPERATIONS

Git, Github, NPM Webpack, Hiroku and Netlify.

EDITOR

Visual Studio

XD

KNOWLEDGE

Python & Typescript

WORK EXPERIENCE

Youth worker Frog Hollow Neighbourhood House 8/2018 - 3/2020

Volunteer Interpreter/Admin Assistant Immigrant Services Society of BC 3/2018 – 4/2018

Guest Relations - Data Management Accor Bullman Zamzam Hotel 8/2017 – 11/2017

EDUCATION

Web Development Boot Camp CodeCore College 2021

Computer science Diploma TVTC, Saudi Arabia 2017 Training on Digital Marketing, TVTC, Saudi Arabia 2016

LANGUAGES

Arabic (native) English (fluent)

SUMMARY:

Jr Web Developer, recent Web Development Bootcamp graduate with experience working on several projects, passionate about solving problems and learning new technologies. Background working with non-profit organizations. I enjoy building games using Python and C++ in my free time.

TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE:

The Social Home – Rental property finder

Frontend: ReactJS, Backend: Node.JS. Database: CMS.

https://thetriviagame.netlify.app/

- Developed and implemented tool which filter options to increase the efficiency and improve client experience.
- Implemented EmilJs tool to receive submissions from clients.
- Implemented content management system technology to store and update data externally.

E-commerce - online store

Frontend: HTML5, CSS3, React, Backend: Redux, Node & Express, Database: MongoDB.

https://github.com/AlmarwaniLa/-ECommerce

- Monitor and improve quality of web components.
- Developed and implemented tool which filter options to increase the efficiency and improve client experience.
- Implemented multiple payment method options to enhance client experience.

Trivia Game- Random trivia categories

Frontend: ReactJS, HTML, CSS Backend: Typescript

https://thetriviagame.netlify.app/

- Implemented API data from Trivia open sources.
- Automatic multiple rounds with displaying scores.

Let's chat - Real Time Messenger

Frontend: React & HTML, Backend: JavaScript, Socket.io.

- Developed interactive interface for multiple clients.
- Developed Custom React localStorage Hook.